# NELSON DALY

#### nelson.daly@outlook.com | nelsond.tech

#### **About Me**

An inquisitive and proactive Front-End Developer, with strong problem-solving skills and experience delivering results in a fast-paced environment. Able to communicate effectively with all levels of seniority and degrees of technical understanding. Experienced in project leadership and stakeholder management.

#### **Skills**

TypeScript / JavaScript | Angular 11+ | HTML5 | CSS3 | RxJS | NgRx | Karma | Jasmine | Java 8

# **Demonstrable Experience**

## Portfolio Web App (nelsond.tech/this.app)

• Developed a Single-Page Application in the style of a code editor, using Angular 13 and TypeScript, featuring a resizable preview section showcasing live demonstrations of the following additional projects built.

### Issue Tracker App (nelsond.tech/issuetracker.app)

• Designed and developed a CRUD web application, featuring vanilla JavaScript chart visualizations.

#### Scientific Calculator App (nelsond.tech/scicalculator.app)

• Created an emulation of Casio fx-991MS. Implemented 80% functionality for the minimum viable product.

#### **Local Weather Forecast App** (nelsond.tech/localweather.app)

• Built a live weather forecast widget, consuming JSON data from a third-party REST API / microservice.

## **Career History**

#### **Enprod**

**Technical Consultant** 

2021 – Present

• Providing varying technical consulting, presently focused on front-end web development using Angular.

#### **Goldman Sachs**

Support – Engineering Division

2013 - 2021

• Provided support to cross-region Engineering teams, across multiple Business Units, for numerous management systems, processes and projects. Developed Confluence, SharePoint and internal websites. Analyzed data and distributed weekly reports.

#### Education

#### University of Pennsylvania

2020 - 2021

- Professional Certificate in Computer Science Essentials for Software Development
  - Certificate for SD1x: Software Development Fundamentals
  - Certificate for SD2x: Data Structures and Software Design
  - Certificate for SD3x: Algorithm Design and Analysis
  - Certificate for SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript

Microsoft 2020

- Certificate for DEV262x: Logic and Computational Thinking
- Certificate for DAT201x: Querying Data with T-SQL
- Certificate for DAT206x: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Excel

#### **British Academy of New Music**

2011 - 2013

• Level 3 RSL Extended Diploma for Music Technology